# JAMSHID KHOSRAVI

### WEB DEVELOPER

(+49)-177-879-0341

jamshid.khosravi1993@gmail.com

Magdeburg, Germany (Open to Relocation)

Portfolio

LinkedIn

GitHub

## SKILLS & TOOLS

#### Front-End:

- HTML, CSS, JS
- Responsive Design
- Bootstrap library
- jQuery
- React, Angular, React Native

#### **Back-End & Databases:**

- Python
- Django
- Node.js
- Express
- API
- MongoDB & SQL
- JSON

## Also proficient in:

- Git
- TDD & BDD
- Postman
- Heroku & Netlify
- SCRUM (Trello)

#### Languages:

- Persian
- English

# PROFILE

Web developer with a background in Civil Engineering. Experience in supervising the construction of structures and working with a team. Creative person with an interdisciplinary background and skilled at problem solving and learning new skills.

# EDUCATION

**Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development** | CareerFoundry, Berlin, Germany, September 2022 - May 2023

M.E. Water Engineering | Magdeburg-Stendal University of Applied Sciences, Magdeburg, Germany, October 2020 - Present
B.S. Civil Engineering | Iran University of Science and Technology,

Tehran, Iran, September 2011 - May 2016

# EXPERIENCE

**Trainee web developer |** CareerFoundry, Berlin, Germany, September 2022 - May 2023

- Intense project-based training program focused on JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools.
- 500+ hours of hands-on training with guidance of industry leading tutor and mentor.
- myFlix App: created a non-relational database (MongoDB) of movies and built REST APIs with Node.js and Express and tested them with Postman and deployed on Heroku.

Worked at Hafar Khak Combaden as an executive engineer | Tehran, Iran, July 2016 - August 2020

- Control of accurate execution of works technically.
- Implement the project schedule and control it.
- Getting executive plans from the technical office to implement them and giving them to the executors.
- Continuous communication with the site manager and giving a detailed report of the works.

**Teaching assistant for "Surveying and Operations"** | Iran University of Science and Technology, Tehran, Iran, October 2013 - March 2014

• Conducting practice solving classes.

Private Tutoring of Math | Tehran, Iran, August 2016 - January 2020

• Teaching mathematics to high school students.

## Voluntary work:

**Teaching Math and Science to cancer children** | Bahrami Hospital, Tehran, Iran, February 2015 - October 2015